simple2profit.com 2015-06-07

# Simple2Advertise Privacy Policy

> _**What information do we collect?**_
> 
> We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form such as in providing feedback, contacting support support or submitting a question regarding your purchases.
> 
> When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.
> 
> _**What do we use your information for?**_
> 
> Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
> 
> • To personalize your experience  
>  (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
> 
> • To improve our website  
>  (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
> 
> • To improve customer service  
>  (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
> 
> • To process transactions
> 
>     The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
> 
> _**How do we protect your information?**_
> 
> We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you purchase from Simple2Advertise.
> 
> We offer the use of a secure server during our checkout process. 
> 
> After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
> 
> Do we use cookies?
> 
> Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
> 
> We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.
> 
> Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
> 
> We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
> 
> _**Who's capture page is this?**_
> 
> The capture pages hosted on this site were created by [Simple2Advertise](http://simple2advertise.com/?rid=), a customizable marketing platform. We allow our users to take our professionally crafted designs and customize them for their own use.
> 
> When you opt in to a users capture page, you are agreeing to be included on their mailing list. It is that affiliates responsibility to allow you to unsubscribe from all future mailings.
> 
> In almost ALL cases, Simple2Advertise itself DOES NOT CAPTURE ANY LEADS. We simply link a capture page with a S2A members' autoresponder system. We never see any of the email addresses entered into affiliate's capture pages, and will never contact an affiliate's leads for our own purposes. Results that are generated are the affiliates prospects who did the marketing to get that person to their capture page. Email addresses entered into a capture page are not shared with any other affiliates or S2A administrators and can not be, since we do not see them..
> 
> In some cases, pages on our website may be linked to other internet marketers' mailing lists. Due to this, we have no control over what they will do with your email.
> 
> Third party links
> 
> Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
> 
> Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
> 
> We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
> 
> Online Privacy Policy Only
> 
> This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
> 
> Your Consent
> 
> By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
> 
> As this is a marketing website, you should assume that every link you click on is an affiliate link and someone is making a commission. Every move you make on these webpages is tracked and analyzed so the pages can be tweaked and modified to perform better. 
> 
> Changes to our Privacy Policy
> 
> If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
